>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们谈谈提升。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let’s
talk about hoisting.
你们有多少人听过这句话 ?
How many of you have heard
the phrase hoisting before?
好的，它被抛出或者被抛出了很长一段时间。
Okay, it is thrown around or has been
thrown around JavaScript for a long time.
此外，变量提升并提升并提升该值。
As well, variables hoist, and
hoisting this and hoisting that.
直到最近一两年内
Until recently,
that is within the last year or two,
字提升机甚至没有出现在 JavaScript 规范中。
the word hoist literally did not even
appear in the JavaScript specification.
因为事实证明吊起并不是一件真实的事情。
Because it turns out that hoisting
is not actually a real thing.
JavaScript 引擎未挂起，
The JavaScript engine does not hoist,
它不会绕它建议吊装的方式移动。
it does not move things around
the way it is suggested with hoisting.
我的坚持是我们所做的一个比喻。
Hoisting is a metaphor
that we have made up.
这是我们所做的语言约定
It is a language convention
that we have made up, and
我是说英语公约
I mean English language convention.
这是我们要讨论的英语语言公约
It is an english language convention
that we have made up to discuss
词法范围的概念，不考虑词法范围，好吗 ?
the idea of lexical scope, without
thinking about lexical scope, okay?
我来告诉你为什么它不存在，为什么不可能呢 ?
And I'll show you why it doesn't actually
exist, why it's really not even possible
因为它有这么简单的代码，它只需要几条线。
for it to exist with this very simple
piece of code, it only takes a few lines.
如果你试图解释第一个是什么
If you try to explain what
happens with line one, and
我们用我们已经讨论过的词法范围的讨论
we use the lexical scope discussion
like we already talked about.
然后，您将首先通过此作为编译器，并且
Then you would first pass through
this as the compiler, and
那你就会把它当作行刑
then you would pass through
it as an execution.
但人们不喜欢做的事情
But what people don't like doing,
it seems,
从两条过去的角度来思考这个问题
is thinking about this
in terms of two passes.
人们似乎想过一次就能通过它
People seem to be wanting to be stuck
on passing through it just once.
两票看起来更乱
Two passes seems more confusing,
只要给我一个有用的解释
just give me an explanation
that works with a single pass.
无论是否属实，我只想更方便地解释。
Whether it's true or not,
I just want a more convenient explanation.
这就是吊装的来源。
And that's where hoisting comes from.
库兹吊装说我们可以解释这里到底发生了什么
Cuz hoisting says, well,
we could explain what really happens here,
如果有这种神奇的行为叫做提升
if there was this magical
behavior called hoisting.
任何时候 JavaScript的执行引擎都进入了一个范围
Which was that any time JavaScript's
execution engine entered a scope,
它神奇地向前看，在任何地方都发现了所有的声明
it magically looked ahead and
found all of the declarations wherever
他们在那个范围内，为他们做了变数，对吧 ?
they were in that scope, and
made variables for them, right?
就像 JavaScript 引擎去发现那些变量声明
So it's as if the JavaScript engine goes
and finds those variable declarations and
在执行前将其移动到作用域的顶部。
moves them to the top of
the scope before execution.
这就是提升吊升的方式。
That's literally how
hoisting is described.
这不是实际发生的事情。
That's not what actually happens.
JavaScript 实际上不会通过向上移动 vars 来重组代码
JavaScript does not actually reorganize
your code by moving the vars up
我可以向你证明这不是发生的事情
to the top, and here is how I can prove
to you that that's not what happens.
因为，这个神奇的前方是如何运作的呢 ?
Because, how would that magical
look ahead actually work?
当它进入代码的时候它会多么的神奇
How would it magically somehow when
it enters the piece of code for
第一次在第一次通过的时候
the very first time on the very first
pass, magically be able to at it and
只会找到宣言吗
only find that declarations?
您当然不能使用正则表达式，因为 JavaScript
You certainly can't use regular
expressions for that, because JavaScript
是一种非正则语言，所以正则表达式不够好。
is a non-regular language so
regular expressions aren't good enough.
那么你要怎么弄清楚那些 vars 是什么地方
So, how are you going to figure
out where all the vars are?
你要做一些非常精细的处理
You're gonna do some very
sophisticated processing
在该块中稍后出现的标记上，直到找到块的末尾。
on the tokens that come later in that
block until you find the end of the block.
然后那些地方可能发生了声明
And then any of those places where
a declaration could have occurred,
然后你就可以把它们拉出来，理论上你可以重新安排和移动这些
then you can pull those out, and you could
theoretically rearrange and move those.
猜猜这个神奇的处理方法会叫什么
And guess what that magical,
fancy processing would be called?
正在解析，好吗 ?
Parsing, okay?
这叫解析
That's called parsing.
如果你想在街区里找到变量声明
If you wanna find the variable
declarations further down in the block,
你唯一能做的就是解析
the only way you can do
that is with parsing.
所以起重并不是一件事情，它是一个简写，一个我们可以用来
So hoisting isn't really a thing, it is a
shorthand, a convention that we can use to
在不需要了解细节的情况下去描述一些事情
try to describe something without needing
to get into the nitty-gritty details.
我不是说这件事很糟糕但很普遍
I'm not saying that it is a bad thing but
what has been rather prevalent,
如我所见，我甚至无法计算 Stack Overflow 的数量。
as I have seen, in, I can't even
count how many Stack Overflow.
当人们问为什么 JavaScript 要做什么
When people asks questions about why
JavaScript is doing something and
看起来很奇怪或者坏了他们发布了一些代码示例
it seems like it's weird or broken,
and they post some code example.
然后有人说这是因为举升的原因
And then somebody says, well,
it's because of the hoisting, and
然后这个人说，好的。
then this person says, Okay.
结果证明他们错了。
And then it turns out
that they're just wrong.
这对你来说可能很意外
This may be surprising to you, but
你知道 Stack Overflow的问题吗
did you know that stuff is
wrong on Stack Overflow?
>> 扬声器 1: [INAUDIBLE]。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: [INAUDIBLE].
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的，令人震惊，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes, shocking,
我应该给你警告下才会掉下这枚知识炸弹
I should have given you warning
before dropping that knowledge bomb.
这是一个事实， Stack Overflow 中存在人员，
This is a fact, there are posts on
Stack Overflow where people have
问了关于我的书的问题你不懂 JS
asked questions about my books,
the You Don't Know JS books.
在其中一个岗位上，很多人，但是在我找到的其中一个职位上，
And on one of those posts, many of them,
but on one of these posts that I found,
这个人说凯尔是什么意思
this person said,
what does Kyle mean when, and
他引述了我在书中所说的一段话。
he quoted some passage that I
was talking about in my book.
我尽量去 Stack Overflow 去检查这些，但是
I try as much as possible on Stack
Overflow to go in and check for these, but
有太多太多的问题我已经失去了对这些问题的关注
there's too many and I have lost
track of triaging questions on,
已使用 " 不了解 JS " 或 " YDKJS" 进行标记。
that have been tagged with
You Don't Know JS, or YDKJS.
所以，我在这个职位上跑了一次，所以这是个问题。
So, I ran across this post-one time,
and so here's this question.
我是写这本书的人我的名字写在书上
And I'm the one that wrote the book,
my name is on the book.
地球上没有人能更权威地处理
There is nobody on the planet that is more
authoritative on the question of what did
我的意思是
I mean than me.
>> 演讲者 2: [LAUGH] >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们能同意吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Can we agree with that?
>> 演讲者 2: 好的地方。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Good point, there.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay?
我对 JavaScript 的错误是否是一个单独的问题，但是
Whether I'm wrong about JavaScript
is a separate issue, but
我是说我是那个规范的权威
what I mean,
I'm the authoritative on the spec, okay?
>> 扬声器 2: [LAUGH] >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 其他人回答了
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Somebody else answered
问题是他们完全错了
the question, and
they were completely wrong.
完全错误的是 100% 。
Just 100% totally wrong.
我不觉得，我不喜欢那个人，人犯错误，
I don't feel, I'm not like down on
that person, people make mistakes,
他们不懂的东西
they don't understand stuff.
但这里的情况是如此的不正常，绿色的复选标记和超过 4000 个的上传。
But here's what was so demoralizing, the
green check mark and over 4000 uploads.
即使我把我的小答案发布到现在也有 17 个上传
Even when I post my little answer
there is now like 17 uploads,
它永远不会被任何人看到
it's never going to get seen by anybody.
所以你不能永远相信你在足球名单上读到的东西
So you can't always trust
what you read on Soccer List.
对不起这小的小问题好吗
Sorry for that little digression, okay?
>> 扬声器 3: 我们可以帮助您。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: We can help you.
我们都能投票给你
We can all upvote you.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的，我们可以得到 100 张选票 [LAUGH ] 。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah,
we can get 100 more votes [LAUGH].
这不可能让我到 4000人
It's not gonna get me to 4000.
但不管怎么说我所做的就是很多问题
But anyway, so, the point that I was
making is there's lots of questions where
人们会问关于这件事的问题他们会说我是
people will ask questions about this
whole hoisting thing, and they'll say I'm
很沮丧因为这不是正确的方法或者我是什么
frustrated because this doesn't seem
to work the right way or what am I.
有人会回答这个问题他们会用吊起
And somebody will answer it and
they'll use hoisting, and
它会使不准确的情况永久化
it will perpetuate inaccuracy.
不是吊装对你没有帮助，但是当你用吊装的时候，
It is not that hoisting is unhelpful
to you, but when you use hoisting, and
你不知道这些细节你不知道到底发生了什么
you don't know the nuances, and
you don't know what's actually happening,
那你就会被误导了
then you actually get misled
into thinking the wrong thing.
这就是我第一次教你这样做的原因
Which is why I first taught
you ow it really works, and
我们如何回到更速记的定义上
how we're circling back to the more
shorthand definition, because armed with
这两个你以后都可以保证你不会搞糊涂的。
both of those, you can make sure in
the future that you don't get confused.
但只携带有吊重的武器只需要几行代码
But armed only with hoisting,
it only takes a few lines of code for
我把开发商搞糊涂了
me to confuse a developer.
所以这件案子不是被搬上来的
So it is not the case
that these get moved up,
就像职能被重新分配一样
just like it is not the case
that functions get reassigned.
如果我们想弄明白它的行为
This code, if we were trying
to figure out what it did,
我们会说根据吊装，这就是它所做的。
we would say according to hoisting,
that this is what it did.
它先移动函数，然后移动变量声明，
It moved the function first, and then
it moved the variable declaration, and
然后它就被处死了
then it executed.
对于完全相同的原因，它不会丢失变量，它不会失去功能。
For the exact same reason it doesn't lose
variables, it doesn't lose functions.
它在第一次传递过程中处理它们，然后执行。
It handle them during the first pass,
and then it execute.
但是，在这张幻灯片上要做的是非常重要的区别。
There is, however, and important
distinction to be made here on this slide,
函数声明和函数表达式之间的差异。
which is the difference between a function
declaration and a function expression.
有几个你在问我们说到错误功能的时候，哎，
A number of you were asking when we were
talking about error functions, hey well,
如果我把我最喜欢的错误函数分配给变量就行了吗
isn't it okay if I just assign my favorite
loving error function to a variable?
还好吗
Is it okay?
嗯。 行吗 ?
Yes.
Will it work?
那得看情况了
It depends.
在此特定示例中，我们具有要移动到顶部的功能，但
In this particular example, we have the
functions having to move to the top, but
请注意第 9 行上的功能分配所发生的情况，
notice what happened to
the function assignment on line 9,
只会在 9 号线路上发生
it's still only happens on line 9.
这意味着第 7 行将抛出类型错误。
Which means that line seven is
going to throw a type error.
那么换句话说，
So in other words,
要使用仅将其分配给属性或变量的函数形式，
to use the form of function where you only
assign it to properties or variables,
您必须先定义所有功能，然后才能对其进行调用。
you have to have all of your functions
defined before you call them.
有些人喜欢这样
Some people like that.
事实上，我的发展生涯可能已经超过 15 年了，
As a matter of fact, for probably more
than 15 years of my development career,
我就是这么做的
I did exactly that.
可能是因为我的编程语言很像 C
Probably because I have roots
in programming languages like C.
我习惯了我所有的功能都在上面
I got used to the habit of having
all my functions at the top, and
我的所有可执行代码都在底部
all my executable code at the bottom.
有一天，大约五年，六年前，大概七年前
And one day, about five, six years ago,
maybe almost seven years ago at this
啊，我一天就知道了，为什么我要把所有的职能都放在上面，
point, it just dawned on my one day, why
am I putting all my functions at the top,
然后每次我打开这个文件
and then every time I open up this file,
在找到可执行代码之前，我要滚动 3000 行吗 ?
I've gotta scroll 3,000 lines before
I can find my executable code?
我为什么不能把那个代码放在上面
Why can't I just put that code at the top,
so
在我打开文件的时候就在那儿吗
it's right there when I open up the file?
这很明显是密码的作用。
And it's real obvious what the code does.
如果我需要看看这些功能，他们还在那里，但是
If I need to look at the functions,
they're still there, but
我想轻松找到可执行代码
I wanna find the executable code easily.
在底部发现它比在顶部找到它要困难得多。
And finding it at the bottom is a lot
of harder than finding it at the top.
所以我就开始把所有功能放在任何范围的底部。
And so I just started putting all
the functions at the bottom of any scope.
我不仅在最重要的范围内这样做，而且在范围内也是这样做的。
And not only do I do that in the top
scope, but I also do that within scopes.
我把可执行代码放在最上面
I put the executable code at the top, and
我把功能声明放在底部
I put my function
declarations at the bottom.
我利用功能提升的优势
And I take advantage of
the fact that functions hoist.
他们在吊重机对吧
They hoist, right?
它们是在编译时进行的，以这样定义的方式进行定义
They are taken at compile time and
defined in such a way so
他们可以在比他们被宣布的范围更早地使用
that they can be used even earlier in
the scope than when they've been declared.
所以有很多很多人说 JavaScript 吊起
So there are many, many people that
say that JavaScript's hoisting
这个机制是一个坏的，设计不好的，模糊的一部分。
mechanism is a bad, poorly designed,
buggy part of the system.
这就是为什么 JavaScript 不符合词汇限定语言的原因
And it's why JavaScript doesn't qualify
as a lexically scoped language because of
我们不应该用它，也不应该依赖它。
hoisting, and we shouldn't use it,
and shouldn't rely upon it.
和大多数事情一样它取决于
And as with most things, it kinda depends,
取决于你对你要完成的事情的看法
it depend on your perspective of
what you're trying to accomplish.
有时吊装是不好的，
It is sometimes the case
that hoisting is bad, and
有时我觉得这很有用
sometimes the case I
think it's quite useful.